# SHAHID AZIZ

Swabi KPK, 23330, Pakistan | +92 3275220112 | shahid.dev.aziz@gmail.com

# Summary

Committed professional offering more than 3+ years of experience in the field of web application development. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents by bringing a wealth of expertise to a well-established company.

### Experience

#### Front-End Developer

Aug 2023 to Current

OzaCloud - Pakistan

- Proficient in JavaScript frameworks such as Next JS, React JS, Tailwind CSS.
- Designed and implemented website interface for mobile, desktop, and tablets.
- Tested links to identify and rectify discrepancies, determine speed, and gauge traffic.

#### Frontend developer

Jan 2024 to Mar 2024

Bren - Michigan , US

- Proficient in JavaScript frameworks such as Next JS, React, Astro and Tailwind Css.
- Designed and implemented website interface for mobile, desktop and tablets.
- Handled special projects designated by senior developer.

#### Front-End Developer

Sep 2023 to Feb 2024

We Krazy - London, UK

- Proficient in JavaScript frameworks such as Next Js, React Js, Tailwind CSS Ember and Backbone.
- Troubleshoot website on different browsers to determine quality.
- Used Figma to structure web pages and provide smooth navigation of theinternet.

#### Skills

- Next Js
- React Js
- Astro Js
- TypeScript
- Vanilla JavaScript
- CSS 3

- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap 5
- GIT
- Website optimisation
- GSAP

#### Education

# Higher Education, Computer Science

2022 to 2024

HCST College - Swabi KPK

# Languages

English, Urdu: First Language

### **Hobbies**

- Traveling
- Cricket